<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>real-life on APPSECRADAR :: HACKING | CODING | BLOGS &amp; GOOD VIBES</title>
    <link>/tags/real-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in real-life on APPSECRADAR :: HACKING | CODING | BLOGS &amp; GOOD VIBES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 14:56:23 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/real-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Solving Intigriti May XSS Challenge without Burp Suite!</title>
      <link>/posts/intigriti-may-xss-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 14:56:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/intigriti-may-xss-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: All the content posted here is strictly for educational purposes only. The author is not responsible for any harm caused using this content in any other way apart from the one intented.
 Introduction The Intigriti May XSS challenge was open from May 11 to May 17. Like the Easter-Challenge, this challenge also took a lot of time for me to understand and replicate. Like many, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve it during the challenge days and waited for someone to post a writeup so that I can follow along and solve it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solving Intigriti Easter XSS Challenge without Burp Suite!</title>
      <link>/posts/intigriti-xss-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:18:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/intigriti-xss-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: All the content posted here is strictly for educational purposes only. The author is not responsible for any harm caused using this content in any other way apart from the one intented.
 Introduction The Intigriti Easter XSS challenge was open from April 13 to Aril 19. I know I&amp;rsquo;m a little late to the party but this challenge took a lot of time for me to understand. Like many, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve it during the challenge days and waited for someone to post a writeup so that I can follow along and solve it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unboxing SolidState</title>
      <link>/posts/htb-walkthrough-solidstate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 10:48:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/htb-walkthrough-solidstate/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Unboxing SolidState; a fun box by creator ch33zplz - This wasn&amp;rsquo;t my first box on HTB but still I&amp;rsquo;ll start my blog series with this. You will come to know why I am giving such an honour to this box. Just stay with me till the end. I thoroughly enjoyed solving this box &amp;amp; the &amp;lsquo;State&amp;rsquo; of satisfaction after getting root was totally something else! I promise, by the end, it will be a &amp;lsquo;Solid&amp;rsquo; stroll down your memory lane!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>